Guide to the Tri-State Conference on Manufacturing Records, 1978-1993 AIS.1993.10
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Industrial Roundtable Draft Background Material (Box 59, Folder 6)
- Industrial Roundtable Draft Proposal and Letter, January 1989 (Box 59, Folder 7)
- Conference Description (Box 59, Folder 8)
- Roundtable Sponsors (Box 59, Folder 9-11)
- Industrial REnaissance Co-Sponsors (Box 59, Folder 12)
- Industrial Roundtable Washington, DC Meeting, July 21, 1989 (Box 59, Folder 13)
- George Meany Center, September 14-15, 1989 (Box 59, Folder 14)
- Industrial Renaissance Project: Modernizing America's Industrial Base (Box 59, Folder 15)
- Economic Conversion: Jobs With Peace State Convention (Box 59, Folder 16)
- Industrial Renaissance Legislative Initiative (Box 59, Folder 17)
- Industrial Renaissance Project: Economic Dislocation and Worker Adjustment Assistance Act/Worker Adjustment and Retraining Notification Act Joint Project (Box 59, Folder 18)
- Economic Conversion Contract Language (Box 59, Folder 19)
- Economic Conversion: Ann Markusen Paper (Box 59, Folder 20)
- Economic Conversion: MA Research (Box 59, Folder 21)
- Pension, Joint Trusteeship (Box 59, Folder 22)
- Pension, Reversions (Box 59, Folder 23)
- Foundations (Box 59, Folder 24)
- Southbank Industry Association Meeting, October 12, 1990 (Box 59, Folder 25)
- South Side Summer Street Spectacular, July 12-15, 1990 (Box 59, Folder 26)
- Southbank Industry Association Members Meeting, March 14, 1990 (Box 59, Folder 27)
- Southbank Industry Association Aquaviva Reception, November 28, 1990 (Box 59, Folder 28)
- Southbank Industry Association Summer Festival, July 13-17, 1989 (Box 59, Folder 29)
- Southbank Industry Association Food Raffle, 1989 (Box 59, Folder 30)
- Southbank Industry Association Weeks Reception, March 20, 1989 (Box 59, Folder 31)
- Southbank Industry Association Membership Brochure (Box 59, Folder 32)
- Bank Statements (Box 59, Folder 33)
- Check Receipts (Box 59, Folder 34)
- Financial Statements (Box 59, Folder 35)
- First South Savings and Loan Information (Box 59, Folder 36)
- Southbank Industry Association Board Lists (Box 59, Folder 37)
- Southbank Industry Association Meeting, 1988-1990 (Box 59, Folder 38-51)
- Employee Stock Ownership Programs (Box 59, Folder 52-58)
- LTv Committee (Box 59, Folder 59-60)
- Regional Reindustrialization Program, Steel: Metals Survey, LTV South Side Works (Box 60, Folder 1)
- Economic Development Organizations: PACE (Box 60, Folder 2)
- Economic Development Organizations: Southern Policies Growth Board (Box 60, Folder 3)
- Economic Development Organizations: Southwestern Pennsylvania Community Loan Fund (Box 60, Folder 4)
- Economic Development Organizations: Worker Owned Network (Box 60, Folder 5)
- Southwestern Pennsylvania Industrial Resource Centers (Box 60, Folder 6)
- Economic Development Models: Community Enterprise Network (Box 60, Folder 7)
- Economic Development Models: ITI Metalworking Study (Box 60, Folder 8)
- Economic Development Models: Manufacturing Networks (Box 60, Folder 9)
- Economic Development: MA Industrial Services Program (Box 60, Folder 10)
- Economic Development: Michigan (Box 60, Folder 11)
- Economic Development Models: Mondragon (Box 60, Folder 12)
- Economic Development Models: Neighborhood Information and Analysis System (Box 60, Folder 13)
- Economic Development Models: Rational Reindustrialization (Box 60, Folder 14)
- Economic Development Models: Regional Economic Models, Inc. (Box 60, Folder 15)
- Economic Development Models: Regional Industry Centers (Box 60, Folder 16)
- Economic Development Models: Shorebank Corporation (Box 60, Folder 17)
- Economic Development Models (Box 60, Folder 18)
- Events: CCAC Reindustrialization Conference (Box 60, Folder 19)
- Events: Nemacolin Conference, University of Pittsburgh (Box 60, Folder 20)
- Pittsburgh City Ordnance on Economic Development (Box 60, Folder 21)
- State of Pennsylvania (Box 60, Folder 22)
- State of Pennsylvania: Anti-Corporation Take Over (Box 60, Folder 23)
- Regional Reindustrialization Programs Pennsylvania Players: State of Pennsylvania (Box 60, Folder 24)
- State of Pennsylvania: Tax Reform (Box 60, Folder 25)
- City of Pittsburgh (Box 60, Folder 26)
- City of Pittsburgh: Pittsburgh Pirates (Box 60, Folder 27)
- Manufacturing Facilities and Companies, Pennsylvania (Box 60, Folder 28)
- Manufacturing Facilities and Companies, Pennsylvania: Park Corporation (Box 60, Folder 29)
- Miscellaneous Papers (Box 60, Folder 30)
- Economic Development Articles: "Industrial Policy and Regional Development" (Box 60, Folder 31)
- MAGLEV (Box 60, Folder 32-50)
- Department of Commerce initiatives Recommended in the Governor's Budget, 1986-1987 (Box 60, Item 1)
- Tri-State Work Group, MAGLEV Notes (Box 61, Folder 1)
- MAGLEV Articles and Press Conferences (Box 61, Folder 2)
- MAGLEV Board Meetings, 1991 (Box 61, Folder 3)
- MAGLEV Inc. Public Finance (Box 61, Folder 4)
- Tri-State and Steel Valley Authority MAGLEV Notes, April 2, 1991 (Box 61, Folder 5)
- Advisory Committees (Box 61, Folder 6)
- Lawrenceville MAGLEV Meeting (Box 61, Folder 7)
- High Speed Rail Conference (Box 61, Folder 8)
- Tri-State Work Group, Regional Reindustrialization Program Notes (Box 61, Folder 9)
- Tri-State/Steel Valley Authority Early Warning Network (Box 61, Folder 10)
- Campaign to Remove Welfare Lien (Box 61, Folder 11)
- Jobs With Justice (Box 61, Folder 12)
- Mon Valley Initiative (Box 61, Folder 13)
- Giant Eagle, Strike and Post-Strike (Box 61, Folder 14)
- Replacing Strikers (Box 61, Folder 15)
- River Cities Legislative Campaign (Box 61, Folder 16)
- Pittsburgh Press Carriers (Box 61, Folder 17)
- Working Conference on Manufacturing (Box 61, Folder 18)
- Federation on Industrial Retention and Renewal, December 1992 (Box 61, Folder 19)
- Regional Reindustrialization Program Update, 1991-1992 (Box 61, Folder 20)
- Regional REindustrialization, 1986 (Box 61, Folder 21)
- Regional Industry Center Meeting in Cleveland, OH (Box 61, Folder 22)
- C. John Kruzeski, Business/Financial Consultant (Box 61, Folder 23)
- Tri-State Grants and Proposals, 1989 (Box 61, Folder 24)
- Bank Statements, 1989 (Box 61, Folder 25-26)
- Time Sheets, 1989 (Box 61, Folder 27)
- Tri-State Finances, 1988-1990 (Box 61, Folder 28-29)
- Tri-State Executive Committee Reports, April-December 1989 (Box 61, Folder 30)
- Tri-State Planning Committee Material, 1989 (Box 61, Folder 31)
- Grant Information, August 1986-December 1988 (Box 61, Folder 32)
- Audit, 1989 (Box 61, Folder 33)
- Tri-State Posted Transaction List, 1990 (Box 61, Item 1)
- Tri-State Finances, 1988-1989 (Box 62)
- Voter Lists (Box 63, Folder 1)
- Calvert Group, Malon Wilkus (Box 63, Folder 2-4)
- Form, Report of Continued Disability (Box 63, Folder 5)
- Form, CARE-Hospital Bill Audit (Box 63, Folder 6)
- Form, Accident Verification (Box 63, Folder 7)
- Form, Assignment of Medical Benefits (Box 63, Folder 8)
- MAGLEV, Community Development Block Grant Town Meetings (Box 63, Folder 9)
- Assignment and Subrogation Agreement for Potential Liability Recovery (Box 63, Folder 10)
- Form, Sick and Accident (Box 63, Folder 11)
- UIU Pension Program (Box 63, Folder 12)
- Prescription Service (Box 63, Folder 13)
- UIU Insurance (Box 63, Folder 14)
- Form, Death Benefit Claims (Box 63, Folder 15)
- Form, Spouse Death Benefit Claims (Box 63, Folder 16)
- UIU and Other Insurance Information (Box 63, Folder 17)
- Form Reorder Cards (Box 63, Folder 18)
- Revised Dependant Registration Cards (Box 63, Folder 19)
- Dependant Listing Cards (Box 63, Folder 20)
- Beneficiary Cards (Box 63, Folder 21)
- Membership Cards (Box 63, Folder 22)
- UIU Summary Books (Box 63, Folder 23)
- Form, UIU Dental Benefits Claim (Box 63, Folder 24)
- Form, UIU Health Care Claim (Box 63, Folder 25)
- UIU Insurance Waiver for Disability Payments (Box 63, Folder 26)
- Study on the Demand and Supply of Semifinished Steel Products in the United States, Final Report, April 30, 1990 (Box 63, Item 1-2)
- Response to the Locker/Abrecht Duquesne Works Feasibility Report by US Steel, 1985 (Box 63, Item 3)
- Steel Initiative Status Report, January 1988 (Box 63, Item 4)
- Steel Initiative Management Plan, April 1, 1987 (Box 63, Item 5)
- Steel Initiative Research Plan, April 1988 (Box 63, Item 6)
- Report to the United Steelworkers of America, Dorothy 6 Financial Feasibility of Reopening the Duquesne Works, January 1986 (Box 63, Item 7-8)
- Feasibility Study of the Duquesne Works' Blast and Basic Oxygen Furnaces for United Steelworkers of America, Preliminary Report, January 28, 1985 (Box 63, Item 9)
- Benefits (Box 64, Folder 1)
- Phoenix Mutual Life Insurance (Box 64, Folder 2)
- Campaign for Human Development, 1986 (Box 64, Folder 3-4)
- Campaign for Human Development, 1988 (Box 64, Folder 5)
- Religious Fundraising: Commission on Religion in Appalachia, 1988 (Box 64, Folder 6)
- Consolidated Natural Gas Foundation (Box 64, Folder 7)
- Religious Fundraising: Episcopals (Box 64, Folder 8)
- Coalition for Human Need, 1985-1988 (Box 64, Folder 9-10)
- The Field Foundation (Box 64, Folder 11)
- George Gund Foundation (Box 64, Folder 12)
- Joyce Foundation (Box 64, Folder 13-14)
- Liberty Hill (Box 64, Folder 15)
- Religious Fundraising: American Lutheran Church (Box 64, Folder 16)
- Religious Fundraising: Methodists (Box 64, Folder 17)
- National Community Funds, Pollock Association (Box 64, Folder 18)
- Religious Fundraising: Fund to Aid Neighbors in Need (Box 64, Folder 19)
- Needmor Foundation (Box 64, Folder 20)
- Pittsburgh Bridge and Iron (Box 64, Folder 21)
- The Pittsburgh Foundation (Box 64, Folder 22)
- Religious Fundraising: Pittsburgh Presbytery Fund for the Self-Development of People (Box 64, Folder 23)
- Shalan Foundation (Box 64, Folder 24)
- Campaign for Human Development, 1987 (Box 64, Folder 25)
- Kim Klein Tapes: Raising Money By Mail (Box 64, Folder 26)
- Miscellaneous Papers (Box 64, Folder 27)
- Regional Reindustrialization Project: Proposal Background Material (Box 64, Folder 28)
- Campaign for Human Development Funding (Box 64, Folder 29)
- Kim Klein Tapes, Special Events (Box 64, Folder 30)
- Fundraising Research (Box 64, Folder 31)
- Foundation Forms (Box 64, Folder 32)
- Pending Grants (Box 64, Folder 33)
- Federation on Industrial Retention and Renewal, Technical Assistance (Box 64, Folder 34)
- Dead Proposals/Letters of Inquiry (Box 64, Folder 35)
- Pending Lettres of Inquiry (Box 64, Folder 36)
- Wellspring, Regional Reindustrialization Program Research (Box 64, Folder 37)
- Wellspring, Regional Reindustrialization Project Research: Cleveland Council of Unemployed Workers, Early Warning Proposal (Box 64, Folder 38)
- Religious Fundraising: Order and Parish Solicitations (Box 64, Folder 39)
- Religious Fundraising: Foundations (Box 64, Folder 40)
- Miscellaneous Foundations (Box 64, Folder 41)
- Tri-State General Fundraising Material (Box 64, Folder 42)
- Kim Klein: How to Formulate Your Case (Box 64, Folder 43)
- Kim Klein Tapes: Finding and Soliciting Major Donors (Box 64, Folder 44)
- Just Harvest Education Fund, 501(c)(3) Application (Box 64, Folder 45)
- Capuchin Justice and Peace Guidelines (Box 64, Folder 46)
- Tri-State Organizational Flow Chart (Box 64, Folder 47)
- Fundraising (Box 65, Folder 1)
- Campaign for Human Development, Local: WABCO Project (Box 65, Folder 2)
- Campaign for Human Development, Local Share Program: Cleveland and Pittsburgh (Box 65, Folder 3)
- Fundraising (Box 65, Folder 4)
- Technology and Structural Unemployment: Reemploying Displaced Adults (Box 65, Item 1)
- Massachusetts Community Development Finance Corporation Investment Programs (Box 65, Item 2)
- Steel Retention Study (Box 65, Item 3)
- Calvert Group, Malon Wilkus (Box 65, Item 4)
- Community Development, Other States (Box 65, Item 5)
- 1st Decade of Century II: 1973-1982, May 1982 (Box 65, Item 6)
- Origins: NC Documentary Service, May 22, 1986 (Box 65, Item 7)
- Report to the Allegheny County Board of Commissioners for the Economic Revitalization of the Monongahela, Youghiogheny, and Turtle Creek Valleys by the Mon Valley Commission, February 1987 (Box 65, Item 8)
- A Strategy for Growth: An Economic Development Program for the Pittsburgh Region, 1984 (Box 65, Item 9-10)
- Pennsylvania State Legislative Budget and Finance Committee Statistical Digest, 1986 (Box 65, Item 11)
- Human Services: Choices for Pennsylvanians, August 1, 1985 (Box 65, Item 12)
- Comprehensive Financial Services For You and Your Business (Box 65, Item 13)
- Steel Valley Debate, April 23, 1988 (Box 65, Item 14)
- Tri-State Finances, 1990-1991 (Box 66)
- Tri-State Budgets, 1989-1991 (Box 67, Folder 1-4)
- Financial Development Plan, 1989-1990 (Box 67, Folder 5)
- Office Inventory, January 7, 1987 (Box 67, Folder 6)
- Tri-State Annual Report, 1990 (Box 67, Folder 7)
- Finance Committee, 1989 (Box 67, Folder 8)
- Kenneth Bergert Job Contract, 1990 (Box 67, Folder 9)
- Employee Stock Ownership Program Contract (Box 67, Folder 10)
- Steel Valley Authority Contract, November 9, 1987 (Box 67, Folder 11)
- Mike Stout Contract, November 1988 (Box 67, Folder 12)
- Bonner Foundation (Box 67, Folder 13)
- Pittsburgh National Bank Credit Application (Box 67, Folder 14)
- Bost Building Urban Redevelopment Authority, 1990 (Box 67, Folder 15)
- The Discount Foundation, 1990 (Box 67, Folder 16)
- Lily Foundation, 1990 (Box 67, Folder 17)
- Charles Bannerman Memorial Fellowship Program - Youth Program, 1990 (Box 67, Folder 18)
- World Vision, 1990 (Box 67, Folder 19)
- Community Development Block Grant, 1990 (Box 67, Folder 20-21)
- Commission on Religion in Appalachia, 1990-1991 (Box 67, Folder 22-24)
- Veatch Program, 1990 (Box 67, Folder 25)
- Campaign for Human Development, 1989-1992 (Box 67, Folder 26-30)
- Budget, 1991 (Box 67, Folder 31)
- MAGLEV Bills, 1989-1991 (Box 67, Folder 32)
- Needmor, 1991 (Box 67, Folder 33)
- Ottinger, 1991 (Box 67, Folder 34)
- A. W. Jones MAGLEV Proposal, March 25, 1992 (Box 67, Folder 35)
- Discount Foundation, 1991 (Box 67, Folder 36)
- Project Extend (Box 67, Folder 37)
- Sunshine Foundation, 1992 (Box 67, Folder 38)
- 3 Rivers Community Fund, September 1991 (Box 67, Folder 39)
- Miscellaneous Papers (Box 67, Folder 40)
- Fr. Richard J. Zelik (Box 67, Folder 41)
- Tri-State Case Statement, 1991-1992 (Box 67, Folder 42)
- Tri-State Annual Appeal, 1991-1992 (Box 67, Folder 43)
- Tri-State Planning and Development (Box 67, Folder 44)
- Tri-State Development Committee Annual Dinner (Box 67, Folder 45)
- Development, St. Joachim Building (Box 67, Folder 46)
- Grnats, 1991 (Box 67, Folder 47)
- Board Development (Box 67, Folder 48)
- MAGLEV In-Kind Reports (Box 67, Folder 49)
- Office Technology Assessment (Box 67, Folder 50)
- Surface Transportation Act (Box 67, Folder 51)
- Transport Research Board (Box 67, Folder 52)
- MAGLEV Environmental Information (Box 67, Folder 53)
- MAGLEV Video (Box 67, Folder 54)
- Public Statements on the National Transportation Policy (Box 67, Item 1)
- Report No. 2 to the MAGLEV Working Group on Federal Developments Affecting High Speed Ground Transportation by Donald M. Itzkoff, October 23, 1989 (Box 67, Item 2)
- Pamphlet- "Homestead- Story of a Steeltown", 1. (Map-case 5, Drawer 4)
- Poster- Recharge Southside Steel, 2.
- Poster- Steel Valley Town Meeting- MAGLEV, 1990; 3.
- Poster- Tri-State Conference on Steel Rock and Roll Benefit, 4-5.
- Poster- Recharge South Side Steel, 6-10.
- Cartoon- Berry's World, 11.
- Map of Harrisburg's Capital Complex, 12.
- Poster for Meeting on MAGLEV Project in McKeesport, 1990; 1. (Map-case 5, Drawer 5)
- Poster for Meeting in Ohio Valley, 1990; 2.
- Poster for MAGLEV Meeting in Duquesne, 1990; 3.
- "Recharge South Side Steel", Poster - United Steelworkers of America, 4.
- 23rd Psalm - Reagan Poster, 1982; 5.
- "Recharge South Side Steel, Put America Back To Work"- Union Poster, 6.
- "Victims of Economic Downturn" Cartoon, 7.
- Poster: Steelworkers Organization of Active Retirees (SOAR), 8.
- Sign for "Tri-state Conference on Steel", 9.
- Protest Signs against LTV Closures for Steel Valley Authority, 10-17.
- Union Posters for U.S. Steelworkers Union, 1986; 18.